Guide to the Harold F. Gosnell Papers 1886-1997
University of Chicago Library
- Series IV: Writings
  - Subseries 1: Books
    - American Parties and Elections -- American Business Leaders -- Correspondence, Manuscript, Typescript, Notes, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - American Parties and Elections -- Labor Leaders -- Correspondence, Clipping, Notes, Typescript, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - American Parties and Elections -- Professionals as Leaders -- Notes, Typescript, Clipping, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - American Parties and Elections -- Negro Leaders -- Solicitations, Typescript, 1967-1968 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - American Parties and Elections -- Negro Leaders -- Typescript, Notes, Research Materials, 1965-1968 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - American Parties and Elections -- Negro Leaders -- Typescript, Notes, Research Materials, 1968-1970 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - American Parties and Elections -- Regulating Lobbies -- Typescript, Notes, Clipping, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - American Parties and Elections -- Suffrage -- Clipping and Typescript, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - American Parties and Elections -- Suffrage -- Typescript and Clippings, 1969-1972 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - American Parties and Elections -- Turnout -- Typescript, undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - American Parties and Elections -- Turnout -- Typescript and Clippings, 1968-1976 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - American Parties and Elections -- Election Laws -- Clippings and Typescript, 1962-1970 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - American Parties and Elections -- Party Finance -- Clippings and Typescript, 1964-1974 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - American Parties and Elections -- Fair Representation -- Clippings and Typescript, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - American Parties and Elections -- Battling Spoils -- Typescript, undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - American Parties and Elections -- The Party in Power -- Clipping, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - American Party Leaders and Followers, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - American Party Systems (with Charles E. Merriam), undated (Box 29, Folder 2-5)
    - American Party Systems, correspondence, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Boss Platt and His New York Machine: A Study of the Political Leadership of Thomas C. Platt, Theodore Roosevelt, and Others, 1922 (Box 29, Folder 7-8)
    - Boss Platt, reviews, 1924 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- Correspondence and Outline, 1951-1952 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- The Record -- Typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- Personality Development -- Typescript and Manuscript, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- Senator -- Clippings, Manuscript, and Typescript, 1955-1962 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- Second Campaign for Senator -- Clippings, Notes, Typescript and Manuscript, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- Entrance -- Typescript and Manuscript, Notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- 1914 Senatorial Election -- Notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- 1920 -- Notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- 1921-1929 -- Clippings, Notes, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- 1928 -- Notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- 1929-1930 -- Notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- The 1932 Chicago Convention -- Notes and Typescript, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- 1932 Campaign -- Article Reprint, 1933 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- New Deal -- Notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- 1936 Campaign -- Notes, Typescript, and Study, undated (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- Elected for a Third Term -- Manuscript, undated (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- Pattern of Success -- Clipping, Typescript, Notes, undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- Figures, 1949 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- Photographs and Illustrations, undated (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- Correspondence, Receipts, Clippings of Reviews, 1952-1961 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- Corrections, Correspondence, Illustrations, Clippings, 1951-1952 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Champion Campaigner: Franklin D. Roosevelt -- Correspondence and Corrections, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Democracy Makes a Difference -- Outline, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Democracy Makes a Difference -- Outlines and Bibliography, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Democracy Makes a Difference/Democracy: Threshold of Freedom -- Manuscript, Typescript, Notes, Article Reprint, 1936-1966 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Democracy Makes a Difference -- Typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Democracy Makes a Difference/Democracy: Threshold of Freedom -- Typescript, Notes, Corrections, Article Reprint, Clipping, 1936-1946 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Democracy Makes a Difference -- Typescript and Manuscript, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Democracy Makes a Difference -- Disenfranchisement -- Notes, Correspondence, 1927-1935 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Democracy Makes a Difference -- Suffrage -- Typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Democracy Makes a Difference -- Women as Office Holders -- Typescript and Manuscript, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Democracy Makes a Difference -- Foreign Born -- Research Materials, 1941-1942 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Democracy Makes a Difference -- Fight for Representation -- Criticism and Notes, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Democracy Makes a Difference -- Legislative Esprit de Corps -- Typescript and Manuscript, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Democracy Makes a Difference -- Appendix -- Typescript and Clipping, 1936 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Democracy Makes a Difference -- Coercive Systems -- Notes and Typescript, undated (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Democracy: The Threshold of Freedom -- Chapters 1-2 -- Correspondence and Typescript, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Democracy: The Threshold of Freedom -- Chapters 3-4 -- Typescript, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Democracy: The Threshold of Freedom -- Chapters 5-6 -- Typescript, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Democracy: The Threshold of Freedom -- Chapters 7-8 -- Typescript, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Democracy: The Threshold of Freedom -- Chapters 9-10 -- Typescript, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Democracy: The Threshold of Freedom -- Chapter 11 -- Typescript and Notes, undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Democracy: The Threshold of Freedom -- Chapters 11-12 -- Typescript, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Democracy: The Threshold of Freedom -- Chapters 13-14 -- Typescript, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Democracy: The Threshold of Freedom -- Chapter 15 -- Typescript, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Democracy: The Threshold of Freedom -- Index -- Typescript, undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Democracy: The Threshold of Freedom -- Preface and Correspondence, 1944-1947 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Democracy: The Threshold of Freedom -- Notes, Annotations, Corrections, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Democracy: The Threshold of Freedom -- Galley Proof, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Democracy: The Threshold of Freedom -- Galley Proof, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Democracy: The Threshold of Freedom -- Chapter 10 Draft, Notes, Correspondence, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Democracy: The Threshold of Freedom -- Correspondence and Notes, 1943-1946 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Franklin Delano Roosevelt biography for children, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Getting Out the Vote -- Outline and Copyright Information, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Getting Out the Vote -- Chapter 6, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Grass Roots Politics, 1940s (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Machine Politics: The Chicago Model -- Correspondence -- Orders, 1961-1966 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Machine Politics: The Chicago Model -- Paperback Edition Correspondence and Publicity, 1967-1968 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Negro Politicians: The Rise of Negro Politics in Chicago -- Research, 1927-1949 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Negro Politicians: The Rise of Negro Politics in Chicago -- Correspondence and Publicity, 1935-1962 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- "History of American Parties," 1929-1962 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- "History of American Parties" and "Period of Republican Advantage," 1967 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- "Origin of Political Interests," 1970 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Drafts of Various Chapters, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- "Methods of Acquiring, Holding and Exercising Political Power Under Changing Technology," 1960-1966 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Regulating Interest Groups, 1960-1966 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Presidential Nominations, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Presidential Nominations, 1952-1964 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Presidential Campaigns, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Election Campaigns, 1952-1963 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Election Campaigns, 1933-1953 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Election Campaigns, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Election Campaigns, 1960-1968 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Election Campaigns, 1965-1966 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Making Laws, 1947-1965 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Making Laws, 1941-1963 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Making Laws, 1964-1968 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Making Laws, 1938-1959 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Making Laws, 1962-1966 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- State Nominations, 1921-1966 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- State Nominations, 1924-1962 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- State Nominations, 1935-1964 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Party Organization, 1937-1940 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Party Organization, 1956-1964 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Party Organization, 1952 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Party Organization, 1961-1966 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Presidential Nominations, 1936-1940 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Suffrage, 1954-1958 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Business Organizations, 1953-1968 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Business Organizations, 1946-1953 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Business Organizations, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Organized Labor, 1959-1966 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Organized Labor, 1961-1974 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Organized Labor, 1966 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Organized Labor, 1945-1967 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Organized Labor, 1944-1966 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Interest Groups, 1960-1966 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Interest Groups, 1964-1966 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Interest Groups, 1939-1967 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Interest Groups, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Presidential Campaigns, 1960-1966 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Influencing Administration, 1946-1963 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Organized Agriculture, 1956-1963 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Organized Agriculture, 1952-1933 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Organized Agriculture, 1962-1965 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Suffrage, 1948-1966 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Suffrage, 1957-1961 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Suffrage, 1936-1963 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Suffrage, 1937-1967 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- American Two-Party System, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Minor Parties, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Fair Representation, 1941-1963 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Demography of Parties, 1952-1962 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Demography of Parties, 1935-1964 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Demography of Parties, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Demography of Parties, 1956-1965 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Demography of Parties, 1938-1964 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Demography of Parties, 1928-1964 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Polls, 1959-1977 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Voters Turnout, 1944-1964 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Safeguards and Abuses, 1949-1962 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Safeguards and Abuses, 1938-1955 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Outline, undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Outline, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Detailed Table of Contents, undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Contents, undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Contents, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Preface and Contents, undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Detailed Table of Contents, undated (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Table of Contents and Preface, undated (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Table of Contents and Preface, undated (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapters 1 and 2, undated (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapters 1 and 2, undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 1, "Introduction to Party Theory," 1966-1973 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 1, "Introduction to Party Theory," undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 1, "Introduction to Party Theory," undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 2, "A Comparison of Two, Multi, and One Party Systems," undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapters 3 and 4, undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapters 3 and 4, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 3, "History of American Parties: The First Century," undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 4, "History Since 1896," 1948-1964 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 4, "History Since 1896," 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 5, "Minor Parties," undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 6, "Geographic, Group, and Traditional Factors," 1948-1970 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapters 5 and 6, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapters 5-8, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 6, "Geographic, Group, and Traditional Factors," 1948-1972 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 7, "Toward a Theory of Parties," undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 8, "Decision Making and the Party Elite," undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 8, "Leaders," 1950-1972 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 8, "Major and Minority Leaders," undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 9, "Methods of Acquiring, Holding, and Exercising Political Power," 1968 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 10, "Party Leadership at Presidential Level," 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 11, "Presidential Nominations," 1964-1973 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 12, "Presidential Elections," 1969-1970 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 13, "Leaders at the Congressional Level," 1964-1975 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 14, "How Congressional Leaders are Chosen," undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 15, "Leaders at the State Level," 1962-1970 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 16, "How State Party Leaders are Chosen," undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 17, "Party Technicians at the National Level," undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 18, " Party Activists at the State and Local Level," 1967-1975 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Chapter 19, "Farmers as Leaders," 1963-1968 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Comments, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Political Parties and the American Creed -- Correspondence, Outlines, Notes, Revisions, 1955-1970 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Political Party Theories and Their Relations to the American Creed -- Chapter 1 -- Photocopied Typescript, undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Political Party Theories and Their Relations to the American Creed -- Chapter 2 -- Photocopied Typescript, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Political Party Theories and Their Relations to the American Creed -- Chapter 3 -- Photocopied Typescript, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Political Party Theories and Their Relations to the American Creed -- Chapter 4 -- Photocopied Typescript, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Political Party Theories and Their Relations to the American Creed -- Chapter 5 -- Photocopied Typescript, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Political Party Theories and Their Relations to the American Creed -- Chapter 6 -- Photocopied Typescript, undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Political Party Theories and Their Relations to the American Creed -- Chapter 7 -- Photocopied Typescript, undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Political Party Theories and Their Relations to the American Creed -- Chapter 8, Pates 1-17 -- Photocopied Typescript, undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Political Party Theories and Their Relations to the American Creed, undated (Box 46, Folder 1-4)
    - Political Party Theories and the American Creed -- Preface and Outline, 1953 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Political Party Theories and the American Creed -- Preface, Outline, Draft, Notes, undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Political Party Theories and the American Creed -- "Political Apprenticeship" and "Chief County Administrator," undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Political Party Theories and the American Creed -- Draft -- Preface-Chapter 4, undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Political Party Theories and the American Creed -- Draft -- Chapter 4-8, undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Illustrations and Preface, undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Preface, undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Draft, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Draft, undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Draft, undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Drafts, Photocopy, and Advertisements, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Draft, Chapters 47-50, undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Draft, Chapters 42-46, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Draft, Chapters 37-41, undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Draft, Chapters 33-36, undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Draft, Chapters 28-32, undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Draft, Chapters 22-24, undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Notes, Drafts, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Manuscript, 1948 Election Campaign, undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Manuscript and Clippings, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Illustrations, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Typescript and Photographs, undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Permissions Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Illustrations, undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Illustrations, undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Truman's Crises: A Political Biography of Harry Truman -- Proofs, undated (Box 49, Folder 8)